thesundaily.my 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy

The Sun Daily – referred to as thesundaily.my (the website, inclusive of other platforms) in this policy – may revise this privacy policy at any time by posting an update on this website. Please check this website from time to time to review the current privacy policy against any preferences you may have indicated. This privacy policy was last updated on July 15, 2017.

**What is this privacy policy for?**

User information is necessary to improve our products. We need to have an accurate picture of the needs and wishes of our users, and to be able to communicate with you. That enables us to offer a service that is relevant and truly interactive. It also helps us to maintain the best possible free-to-user access to the website.

**Should I read any other information and terms?**

Whenever you use the website, information may be collected through the use of cookies. You can read our Cookie Policy for more information about this.

**What information will you collect about me?**

We may ask you to provide personal information on a voluntary basis in order to get a clearer picture of our users.

It is then entirely up to you whether you are happy to give us this information. For example, in the course of certain activities such as commenting on the website, entering competitions, promotions and other offers or submitting content to the website you will be asked to give some details about yourself (for example, email address, name, postcode or year of birth).

You may also choose to email us or make contact with us in other ways. Such contact gives us information about you. We will explain to you why we would like this information and what we do with it at each stage.

If you have any financial dealings, for instance, if you make purchases with our trading partners on co-branded websites, the information you submit will be disclosed to us and to relevant third parties, for example suppliers of goods and services and our web service providers.

Please do not submit your personal information to us if you do not want us to collect it.

We automatically collect some data about our users' browsing actions and patterns. This is aggregate data and does not identify any individual. We do this using web beacons or cookies through a number of carefully selected, trusted third parties.

We also collect information from social media activity such as when you "like" the website, share content or follow us on Twitter. When you sign in to the website using social media you grant permission to the social network to share your user details. Depending on the network this will include basic account information such as name, email address, date of birth and any other details you choose to share according to your particular social media account settings.

**How will this information be used?**

We use the aggregate audience details (where no individual is identifiable) to help us improve our understanding of our users and what they want. We may use it to assist us in arranging more personalised advertising, commercial opportunities and competitions which help us keep the website free for you to enjoy.

We also use this information to ensure we provide the best possible content, tailoring where we can to our users interests. It also helps us develop the website and audit its use.

The information about you as an identifiable individual, including contact details, may be used in a number of ways, including:

* Verifying your identity (for example when you return to the website)

* Personalising your visits to the website and developing the design and style of the website to improve the services provided to you

* Informing you about the latest changes to the website, or products, services or promotional offers that you might find interesting

* Dealing with, and responding to you about, a comment you have submitted for and other such user generated content facilities

* Enabling you to share our content with others using social media or email

* Informing you if you have been successful in any website competitions or promotions

* Compiling customer reviews

* Conducting market research

**Will I receive spam?**

We will not send you any unsolicited marketing.

Please note that registered users may receive important information about thesundaily.my (such as changes to thesundaily.my service or other administration matters). As a registered user, this is not spam.

**How long do you keep my personal information?**

We will keep your information only for as long as it is relevant and useful for the purpose for which it was originally collected.

**What security measures do you use?**

The transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for this.

**Who will you share my personal information with?**

By using the website, you agree that we may disclose your personal information to any company within thesundaily.my group of companies.

Advertisers and advertising networks sometimes require data to select and serve relevant advertisements to you and others. However, we do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to comply with applicable laws (such as the Personal Data Protection Act 2010) and government or regulatory bodies' lawful requests for information.

We may also have to release information (which could include the contents of email communications between any persons) because of a legal requirement on us or pursuant to a court order.

We may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganisation of our business.

**Will my data be sent overseas?**

The Internet does not recognise national boundaries. Services on the Net are accessible globally so collection and transmission of personal data is not always confined to one country.

You should be aware that by using the website and those of our partners or any website we link through to, your personal data may be processed in or transferred to other countries, and you agree to your personal data being transferred or processed in this way, at your own risk.

**What do I do if I am not happy for you to share information about me with others?**

You can email [admin@thesundaily.com](mailto:admin@thesundaily.com) at any time to let us know of any objections you may have as to how we use or disclose your data in the ways set out in this privacy policy.

**User generated content**

User generated content facilities, such as comments, videos, and etc, are made available to users of the website and registered users can provide content for and participate in these facilities. Any information that is disclosed in these areas of our website becomes public information and you should always be careful when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Email a friend and share these article facilities**

When you use these facilities and provide us with personal data (for example, name and email address) of a third party, please ensure that you have their consent before giving us their details and we do not accept any responsibilities or liability for this.

**Other Websites**

The website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for them. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Notice to EU Individuals:**

This Privacy Statement and its enumerated policies are intended to comply with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 (the “General Data Protection Regulation” or “GDPR”) and provide appropriate protection and care with respect to the treatment of your user information in accordance with the GDPR.

As outlined in this Privacy Statement, thesundaily.my will not process your user information without a lawful basis to do so, as such bases are defined in Article 6 of the GDPR. In general, thesundaily.my will process your user information on the legal bases of consent, contract (if you have entered into an agreement with us and such processing is a necessary part thereof), or legal obligation (as noted above). thesundaily.my may also process certain user information on the basis of the following legitimate interests, provided that such interests are not overridden by your privacy rights and interests: delivering and continuing to develop and improve the Site, learning from your behavior on the Site (e.g., analysing traffic) to better serve you and other Site users, helping us modify or enhance the Site and its content, receiving insight as to what users do (and don't) like about our Site or aspects thereof, and providing a stable, consistent, and secure user experience in connection with the Site.

**Further information**

If you want further information, or wish to communicate with us about this privacy policy and your wishes about your personal information, please email us at [admin@thesundaily.com](mailto:admin@thesundaily.com).
